Rose Gerlach Slide Collection
Yale University Arts Library
- Rosenquist, James, b. 1933 (20 slides) (Box 7)
  - AFA, 1966 (Box 7)
  - Castelli gallery, 1966, 1969, 1970 (Box 7)
- Roser, Ce (11 slides) (Box 7)
  - Ruth White gallery, 1964, 1967 (Box 7)
- Ross, Charles, b. 1937 (12 slides) (Box 7)
  - Dwan gallery, 1968, 1969, 1972 (Box 7)
- Rot, Dieter, 1930-1998 (1 slide) (Box 7)
  - AFA, 1966 (Box 7)
- Rotenberg (2 slides) (Box 7)
  - XX Cent West gallery, 1968 (Box 7)
- Roth, David, b. 1942 (4 slides) (Box 7)
  - Elkon gallery, 1972 (Box 7)
- Roth, Frank, b. 1936 (22 slides) (Box 7)
  - Jackson gallery, 1967, 1968, 1970, 1971 (Box 7)
- Rothenberg, Susan, b. 1945 (10 slides) (Box 7)
  - Willard gallery, 1974, 1976, 1979, 1981, 1982, 1983 (Box 7)
- Rougemont (2 slides) (Box 7)
  - Byron gallery, 1966 (Box 7)
- Ruben (1 slide) (Box 7)
  - Schaefer gallery, 1964 (Box 7)
- Ruben, Richard (4 slides) (Box 7)
  - Poindexter gallery, 1969 (Box 7)
- Rückriem, Ulrich, b. 1938 (1 slide) (Box 7)
  - Paula Cooper gallery, 1972 (Box 7)
- Ruda, Edwin, b. 1922 (6 slides) (Box 7)
  - Paula Cooper gallery, 1971, 1973 (Box 7)
- Ruddick, Dorothy, b. 1925 (3 slides) (Box 7)
  - Graham gallery, 1972 (Box 7)
- Rudge, John (3 slides) (Box 7)
  - Byron gallery, 1969 (Box 7)
- Russel, James (29 slides) (Box 7)
  - Ruth White gallery, 1964, 1965, 1967 (Box 7)
- Russo (2 slides) [Slide box 38] (Box 7)
  - Allan Stone gallery, 1970 (Box 7)
- Ryman, Robert, b. 1930 (7 slides) (Box 7)
  - Fischbach gallery, 1969, 1970 (Box 7)
  - Dwan gallery, 1971 (Box 7)
  - Weber gallery, 1 (Box 7)
- Saff, Donald J., b. 1937 (5 slides) (Box 7)
  - Martin gallery, 1966 (Box 7)
- Saito (2 slides) (Box 7)
  - Emmerich gallery, 1972 (Box 7)
- Salle, David, b. 1952 (3 slides) (Box 7)
  - Mary Boone gallery, 1984, 1985 (Box 7)
- Samaras, Lucas, b. 1936 (36 slides) (Box 7)
  - Green gallery, 1964 (Box 7)
  - Pace gallery, 1966, 1968, 1970, 1971 (Box 7)
- Sandback, Frederick Lane, 1943-2003 (1 slide) (Box 7)
  - Dwan gallery, 1969 (Box 7)
- Sander, Ludwig, 1906-1975 (18 slides) (Box 7)
  - Sachs gallery, 1968, 1969 (Box 7)
  - L. Rubin gallery, 1970, 1972 (Box 7)
- Sanders, Joop, b. 1922 (5 slides) (Box 7)
  - Schaefer gallery, 1968 (Box 7)
- Sansegundo (2 slides) (Box 7)
  - Sachs gallery, 1965 (Box 7)
- Santomaso, Giuseppe, 1907-1990 (10 slides) (Box 7)
  - Borgenicht gallery, 1968 (Box 7)
- Saret, Alan, b. 1944 (8 slides) (Box 7)
  - Bykert gallery, 1968, 1970 (Box 7)
- Sarfaty (6 slides) (Box 7)
  - Selected Artists, 1968 (Box 7)
- Sargeant, Jane, b. 1913 (also Sargent) (Ninas, Jane) (3 slides) (Box 7)
  - Bodley gallery, 1969, 1971 (Box 7)
- Saroff (1 slide) (Box 7)
  - Amel gallery, 1965 (Box 7)
- Sato (6 slides) (Box 7)
  - Willard gallery, 1969 (Box 7)
- Saul, Peter, b. 1934 (4 slides) (Box 7)
  - Frumkin gallery, 1964, 1966, 1969 (Box 7)
- Saunders (1 slide) (Box 7)
  - Dintenfass gallery, 1969 (Box 7)
- Savage, Lee (6 slides) (Box 7)
  - Krasner gallery, 1968 (Box 7)
- Sazegar, Morteza (also Mortesa) (5 slides) (Box 7)
  - Poindexter gallery, 1967, 1969 (Box 7)
- Scarfe, Gerald, b. 1936 (16 slides) (Box 7)
  - Waddell gallery, 1968, 1970 (Box 7)
- Schanker, Louis, b. 1903 (3 slides) (Box 7)
  - Schaeffer gallery, 1965, 1973 (Box 7)
- Schapiro (4 slides) (Box 7)
  - Bodley gallery, 1966 (Box 7)
- Schapiro, Miriam, b. 1923 (20 slides) (Box 7)
  - Emmerich gallery, 1967, 1969, 1971 (Box 7)
- Scheggi, Paolo, 1940-1971 (3 slides) (Box 7)
  - Bonino gallery, 1966 (Box 7)
- Schmidt (5 slides) (Box 7)
  - FDU, 1965 (Box 7)
- Schnabel, Julian, b. 1951 (7 slides) (Box 7)
  - Pace gallery, 1984 (Box 7)
  - Schaefer gallery, 1967 (Box 7)
- Schnakenberg, Henry, 1892-1970 (1 slide) (Box 7)
  - Kraushaar gallery, 1969 (Box 7)
- Schneebaum (13 slides) (Box 7)
  - Peridot gallery, 1965, 1966 (Box 7)
- Schneider (2 slides) (Box 7)
  - Rehn gallery, 1966 (Box 7)
- Schnell, Marianne (3 slides) (Box 7)
  - Bodley gallery, 1972 (Box 7)
- Schoener, Jason, 1919-1997 (9 slides) [Slide box 39] (Box 7)
  - Midtown gallery, 1966, 1969 (Box 7)
- Schoffer, Nicholas, b. 1912 (8 slides) (Box 7)
  - Jewish Museum, 1965 (Box 7)
  - Waddell gallery, 1970 (Box 7)
- Schonzeit, Ben, b. 1942 (2 slides) (Box 7)
  - French gallery, 1972 (Box 7)
  - Hoffman gallery, 1973 (Box 7)
- Schrag, Karl, b. 1912 (8 slides) (Box 7)
  - Kraushaar gallery, 1966 (Box 7)
- Schreiber, Martin (10 slides) (Box 7)
  - Spectrum gallery, 1967, 1971 (Box 7)
- Schulman, Morris (2 slides) (Box 7)
  - Feigen-Herbert gallery, 1964 (Box 7)
- Schultze (11 slides) (Box 7)
  - Wise gallery, 1965 (Box 7)
- Schumacher (5 slides) (Box 7)
  - Lefebre gallery, 1968 (Box 7)
- Schwartz, Therese (4 slides) (Box 7)
  - East Hampton gallery, 1966 (Box 7)
  - Sachs gallery, 1969 (Box 7)
- Schwedler, William, 1942-1982 (4 slides) (Box 7)
  - Kornblee gallery, 1972 (Box 7)
- Schwitters, Kurt, 1887-1948 (1 slide) (Box 7)
  - "Merz Drawing," 1924 (Box 7)
- Scott, Tim, b. 1937 (6 slides) (Box 7)
  - Rubin gallery, 1969, 1971, 1973 (Box 7)
- Scott, William (2 slides) (Box 7)
  - Jackson gallery, 1973 (Box 7)
- Seawright, James, b. 1936 (6 slides) (Box 7)
  - Stable gallery, 1966, 1970 (Box 7)
- Secter, Michael (2 slides) (Box 7)
  - Spectrum gallery, 1972 (Box 7)
- Sedgley, Peter, b. 1930 (16 slides) (Box 7)
  - Wise gallery, 1965, 1966 (Box 7)
- Seeman (2 slides) (Box 7)
  - East Hampton gallery, 1967 (Box 7)
- Seery, John, b. 1941 (7 slides) (Box 7)
- Segy, Ladislas, b. 1904 (5 slides) (Box 7)
  - Ruth White gallery, 1966 (Box 7)
- Sekine (5 slides) (Box 7)
  - Staempfli gallery, 1966 (Box 7)
- Seley, Jason, 1919-1983 (5 slides) (Box 7)
  - Kornblee gallery, 1969 (Box 7)
- Seliger, Charles, b. 1926 (6 slides) (Box 7)
  - Willard gallery, 1966 (Box 7)
- Seligman, Kurt, 1900-1962 (1 slide) (Box 7)
  - Myers gallery, 1971 (Box 7)
- Sellers (3 slides) (Box 7)
  - Radich gallery, 1968 (Box 7)
- Sellers, William (4 slides) (Box 7)
  - Hutchinson gallery, 1971 (Box 7)
- Serra, Richard, b. 1939 (2 slides) (Box 7)
  - Castelli Warehouse, 1968 (Box 7)
- Seyfried (5 slides) (Box 7)
  - Schaeffer gallery, 1970, 1971 (Box 7)
- Shao Yu Hsien (9 slides) (Box 7)
  - Jason gallery, 1966 (Box 7)
- Shahly, Jehan (2 slides) (Box 7)
  - Green Mt. Gallery, 1973 (Box 7)
- Shapiro, Joel, b. 1941 (2 slides) (Box 7)
  - Paula Cooper gallery, 1972 (Box 7)
- Sharits (1 slide) (Box 7)
  - Bykery gallery, 1972 (Box 7)
- Sharrer, Honore, b. 1920 (3 slides) (Box 7)
  - Dintenfass gallery, 1969 (Box 7)
- Shatter, Susan, b. 1943 (2 slides) (Box 7)
  - Fischbach gallery, 1980 (Box 7)
- Shaw, Charles Green, 1892-1974 (9 slides) (Box 7)
  - Schaeffer gallery, 1968, 1971 (Box 7)
- Shaw, George Kendall, b. 1924 (11 slides) (Box 7)
  - Tibor de Nagy gallery, 1967, 1968, 1969, 1972 (Box 7)
- Shaw, Robert, b. 1949 (6 slides) (Box 7)
  - Schaefer gallery, 1966 (Box 7)
- Shields, Alan J., 1944-2005 (1 slide) (Box 7)
  - Paula Cooper gallery, 1971 (Box 7)
- Shostak, Edwin Bennett, b. 1941 (2 slides) (Box 7)
  - Fischbach gallery, 1971 (Box 7)
- Shunney, Andrew, 1916-1979 (21 slides) [Slide box 40] (Box 7)
  - Hammer gallery, 1967, 1969 (Box 7)
- Shunney, William (2 slides) (Box 7)
  - Hammer gallery, 1971 (Box 7)
- Shute, Roberta (7 slides) (Box 7)
  - Spectrum gallery, 1968 (Box 7)
- Sicard, Pierre, b. 1900 (1 slide) (Box 7)
  - Hammer gallery, 1967 (Box 7)
- Siegel (5 slides) (Box 7)
  - Radich gallery, 1967 (Box 7)
- Siegel, Alan (2 slides) (Box 7)
  - Hoffman gallery, 1973 (Box 7)
- Siegel, Marietta Warner (1 slide) (Box 7)
  - Hutchinson gallery, 1972 (Box 7)
- Siemanowski, Raymond, b. 1938 (4 slides) (Box 7)
  - Frumkin gallery, 1968 (Box 7)
- Sigueira (6 slides) (Box 7)
  - Viviano gallery, 1966 (Box 7)
- Sildar (2 slides) (Box 7)
  - Sachs gallery, 1966 (Box 7)
- Sills, Thomas Albert, 1914-2000 (3 slides) (Box 7)
  - Bodley gallery, 1970 (Box 7)
- Simicki (1 slide) (Box 7)
  - Vercel gallery, 1968 (Box 7)
- Simon, Alyce (14 slides) (Box 7)
  - A. Funt gallery, 1966 (Box 7)
- Simons, Vera (3 slides) (Box 7)
  - Waddell gallery, 1971 (Box 7)
- Simpson (4 slides) (Box 7)
  - Elkon gallery, 1964 (Box 7)
- Simson, Belvyn (2 slides) (Box 7)
  - Bodley gallery, 1971 (Box 7)
- Sinaiko (2 slides) (Box 7)
  - Bodley gallery, 1964 (Box 7)
- Sivalax (8 slides) (Box 7)
  - Cordier-Ekstrom gallery, 1968 (Box 7)
- Skaling (8 slides) (Box 7)
  - Ruth White gallery, 1964 (Box 7)
- Sklar-Weinstein (1 slide) (Box 7)
  - West Broadway gallery, 1973 (Box 7)
- Slavin (2 slides) (Box 7)
  - Fischbach gallery, 1973, 1974 (Box 7)
- Slutzky, Robert, b. 1929 (1 slide) (Box 7)
  - Schaefer gallery, 1972 (Box 7)
- Smith, David, 1906-1965 (1 slide) (Box 7)
  - Paula Cooper gallery, 1971 (Box 7)
- Smith, Kimber, b. 1922 (1 slide) (Box 7)
  - Emmerich gallery, 1973 (Box 7)
- Smith, Leon Polk, 1906-1996 (4 slides) (Box 7)
  - Chalette gallery, 1964 (Box 7)
  - Denise Rene gallery, 1973 (Box 7)
- Smith, Richard, b. 1929 (14 slides) (Box 7)
  - Feigen gallery, 1966, 1968, 1971 (Box 7)
  - O.K. Harris gallery, 1974 (Box 7)
- Smith, Tony (1 slide) (Box 7)
  - Fischbach gallery, 1968 (Box 7)
- Smythe (1 slide) (Box 7)
  - Radich gallery, 1966 (Box 7)
- Small, Neal (5 slides) (Box 7)
  - Byron gallery, 1969 (Box 7)
- Smithson, Robert, 1938-1973 (18 slides) (Box 7)
  - Dwan gallery, 1966, 1967, 1968, 1969 (Box 7)
  - Weber gallery, 1971, 1972 (Box 7)
- Snelson, Kenneth D., b. 1927 (30 slides) (Box 7)
  - Dwan gallery, 1966, 1970 (Box 7)
  - Bryant Park sculpture, 1968 (Box 7)
  - Weber gallery, 1972 (Box 7)
- Sniderman (2 slides) (Box 7)
  - Krasner gallery, 1968 (Box 7)
- Snow, Michael, b. 1929 (4 slides) (Box 7)
  - Poindexter gallery, 1968 (Box 7)
  - Bykert gallery, 1971 (Box 7)
- Snyder, Joan, b. 1940 (3 slides) (Box 7)
  - Paley and Lowe gallery, 1971 (Box 7)
- Sobrino (1 slide) (Box 7)
  - Denise Rene gallery, 1971 (Box 7)
- Soho (1 slide) (Box 7)
  - 1971 (Box 7)
- Solomon, Hyde, b. 1911 (18 slides) (Box 7)
  - Poindexter gallery, 1967, 1969 (Box 7)
- Solomon, Mosha (6 slides) [Slide box 41] (Box 7)
  - Ruth White gallery, 1967 (Box 7)
- Somberg (6 slides) (Box 7)
  - Poindexter gallery, 1968 (Box 7)
- Sonnenberg, Jack (14 slides) (Box 7)
  - Byron gallery, 1968 (Box 7)
  - Fischbach gallery, 1973 (Box 7)
- Sonnier, Keith, b. 1941 (1 slide) (Box 7)
  - Fischbach gallery, 1966 (Box 7)
- Soress (3 slides) (Box 7)
  - Greer gallery, 1964 (Box 7)
- Soshama (10 slides) (Box 7)
  - Ruth White gallery, 1967 (Box 7)
- Soto, Jesus Rafael, b. 1923 (4 slides) (Box 7)
  - Jackson gallery, 1971 (Box 7)
  - Denise Rene gallery, 1974 (Box 7)
- Soviak, Harry, 1935-1984 (4 slides) (Box 7)
  - Feigen gallery, 1967 (Box 7)
- Soythed (2 slides) (Box 7)
  - Castagna gallery, 1966 (Box 7)
- Spalatin, Marco, b. 1945 (2 slides) (Box 7)
  - Landry-Bonino gallery, 1972 (Box 7)
- Spyropoulis, Yiannis, 1912-1990 (3 slides) (Box 7)
  - Byron gallery, 1969 (Box 7)
- Squires (4 slides) (Box 7)
  - East Hampton gallery, 1969 (Box 7)
- Stadler, Albert, b. 1923 (8 slides) (Box 7)
  - Poindexter gallery, 1969, 1970 (Box 7)
- Stangle, Jack (2 slides) (Box 7)
  - Willard gallery, 1968 (Box 7)
- Stamos, Theodoros, 1922-1997 (10 slides) (Box 7)
  - Emmerich gallery, 1966, 1968, 1970 (Box 7)
- Stanczak, Julian, b. 1928 (17 slides) (Box 7)
  - Martha Jackson gallery, 1964, 1965, 1968 (Box 7)
- Stankiewicz, Richard Peter, 1922-1983 (2 slides) (Box 7)
  - Zabriskie gallery, 1972 (Box 7)
- Stanley, M. (2 slides) (Box 7)
  - Hutchinson gallery, 1973 (Box 7)
- Stazewski, Henryk, 1894-1988 (3 slides) (Box 7)
  - D'Arcy gallery, 1 (Box 7)
- Steffen (7 slides) (Box 7)
  - Palari-Woodstock gallery, 1964 (Box 7)
- Steiner (5 slides) (Box 7)
  - Dwan gallery, 1968 (Box 7)
- Steir, Pat, b. 1938 (2 slides) (Box 7)
  - Graham gallery, 1969 (Box 7)
- Stella, Frank, b. 1936 (20 slides) (Box 7)
  - AFA, 1966 (Box 7)
  - Castelli, 1966, 1967, 1973 (Box 7)
  - Rubin gallery, 1970, 1971 (Box 7)
- Stern, Marina (23 slides) (Box 7)
  - Amel gallery, 1965, 1966 (Box 7)
- Stevenson, Harold, b. 1929 (9 slides) (Box 7)
  - Iolas gallery, 1965 (Box 7)
- Stevenson, John (1 slide) (Box 7)
  - Royal Marks gallery, 1969 (Box 7)
- Stevenson, Robert (1 slide) (Box 7)
  - East Hampton gallery, 1968 (Box 7)
- Stever, Jorge, b. 1940 (3 slides) (Box 7)
  - O.K. Harris gallery, 1973 (Box 7)
- Stewart, Jack (6 slides) (Box 7)
  - Grippi-Waddell gallery, 1964 (Box 7)
- Stoller (5 slides) (Box 7)
  - Ruth White gallery, 1965 (Box 7)
- Stone, Sylvia, b. 1928 (5 slides) (Box 7)
  - Tibor de Nagy gallery, 1967, 1969 (Box 7)
- Streeter, Tal, b. 1934 (7 slides) (Box 7)
  - Amel gallery, 1966 (Box 7)
  - Sachs gallery, 1968, 1972 (Box 7)
- Strick, Racelle (6 slides) (Box 7)
  - Rose Fried gallery, 1966, 1969 (Box 7)
- Strider, Marjorie, b. 1934 (8 slides) [Slide box 42] (Box 7)
  - Pace gallery, 1965 (Box 7)
  - Hoffman gallery, 1973 (Box 7)
- Strombotne, James, b. 1934 (3 slides) (Box 7)
  - Schaefer gallery, 1968 (Box 7)
- Stroud, Peter, b. 1921 (4 slides) (Box 7)
  - Hutchinson gallery, 1970, 1972 (Box 7)
- Suga (7 slides) (Box 7)
  - Mi Chou gallery, 1968 (Box 7)
- Sugai, Kumi, 1919-1996 (8 slides) (Box 7)
  - Lefebre gallery, 1967 (Box 7)
- Sugarman, George, 1912-1999 (20 slides) (Box 7)
  - Radich gallery, 1964, 1966 (Box 7)
  - Fischbach gallery, 1967, 1968, 1969 (Box 7)
  - Zabriskie gallery, 1974 (Box 7)
- Sullivan, Jim (3 slides) (Box 7)
  - Paley and Lowe gallery, 1971 (Box 7)
- Sumers (1 slide) (Box 7)
  - Nordness gallery, 1964 (Box 7)
- Sutej, Miroslav, b. 1936 (2 slides) (Box 7)
  - Arras gallery, 1973 (Box 7)
- Suttman, Paul, 1933-1993 (3 slides) (Box 7)
  - Dintenfass gallery, 1969 (Box 7)
- Swain, Robert, b. 1940 (2 slides) (Box 7)
  - Fischbach gallery, 1968 (Box 7)
- Sweeney, Michael (2 slides) (Box 7)
  - 100 Acres gallery, 1971 (Box 7)
- Syverson (2 slides) (Box 7)
  - Bykert gallery, 1966 (Box 7)
- Tadaki (1 slide) (Box 7)
  - Sachs gallery, 1966 (Box 7)
- Tadasky (13 slides) (Box 7)
  - Fischbach gallery, 1966, 1969 (Box 7)
- Taggart, Terry (3 slides) (Box 7)
  - Reese Palley gallery, 1971 (Box 7)
- Takai (9 slides) (Box 7)
  - Poindexter gallery, 1968 (Box 7)
- Takis, b. 1925 (13 slides) (Box 7)
  - Iolas gallery, 1964 (Box 7)
  - Wise gallery, 1967, 1969, 1970 (Box 7)
- Tallman (9 slides) (Box 7)
  - Byron gallery, 1965 (Box 7)
- Tanaka (2 slides) (Box 7)
  - Staempfli gallery, 1965 (Box 7)
- Tangen, Peter (6 slides) (Box 7)
  - Schaefer gallery, 1966 (Box 7)
- Tangen, Willard (1 slide) (Box 7)
  - Allan Stone gallery, 1964 (Box 7)
- Tania (2 slides) (Box 7)
  - Schaefer gallery, 1966 (Box 7)
- Tanner, V. (2 slides) (Box 7)
  - Sachs gallery, 1965 (Box 7)
- Tanning, Dorothea, b. 1910 (1 slide) (Box 7)
  - Iolas gallery, 1965 (Box 7)
- Tapies, Antoni, b. 1923 (4 slides) (Box 7)
  - Jackson gallery, 1968, 1970 (Box 7)
- Tate, Ralph M. (4 slides) (Box 7)
  - Schaeffer gallery, 1968 (Box 7)
- Tauss, Charles (2 slides) (Box 7)
  - 141 Prince St. gallery, 1973 (Box 7)
- Taylor, Brian, b. 1935 (5 slides) (Box 7)
  - Krasner gallery, 1969 (Box 7)
- Taylor, Evelyn (3 slides) (Box 7)
  - Bodley gallery, 1969 (Box 7)
- Teichman, Sabina, 1905-1983 (5 slides) (Box 7)
  - ACA, 1969 (Box 7)
- Tharrats, Joan Josep, b. 1918 (5 slides) (Box 7)
  - Schaeffer gallery, 1964 (Box 7)
- Thek, Paul, 1933-1988 (9 slides) (Box 7)
  - Pace gallery, 1966 (Box 7)
  - Stable gallery, 1969 (Box 7)
  - A. Stone gallery, 1970 (Box 7)
- Thiebaud, Wayne, b. 1920 (10 slides) (Box 7)
  - Allan Stone gallery, 1968, 1970, 1972 (Box 7)
- Thomas (1 slide) (Box 7)
  - East Hampton gallery, 1968 (Box 7)
- Thomas, Alice (2 slides) (Box 7)
  - Jason gallery, 1967 (Box 7)
- Thomas, Yvonne, b. 1913 (11 slides) (Box 7)
  - Fried gallery, 1965 (Box 7)
- Thompson, Robert, 1937-1966 (7 slides) (Box 7)
  - M. Jackson gallery, 1968 (Box 7)
- Thornhill, Anna (3 slides) (Box 7)
  - Meisel gallery, 1973 (Box 7)
- Thon, William, 1906-2000 (23 slides) [Slide box 43] (Box 8)
  - Midtown gallery, 1966, 1968, 1970 (Box 8)
- Thumim (5 slides) (Box 8)
  - Bodley gallery, 1968 (Box 8)
- Ting, Walasse, b. 1929 (29 slides) (Box 8)
  - Jackson gallery, 1964 (Box 8)
  - Lefebre gallery, 1966, 1967, 1968, 1969, 1971, 1973 (Box 8)
- Tinguely, Jean, 1925-1991 (2 slides) (Box 8)
  - Iolas gallery, 1964, 1965 (Box 8)
- Todd, Michael, b. 1935 (2 slides) (Box 8)
  - Reese Palley gallery, 1971 (Box 8)
  - Zabriskie gallery, 1974 (Box 8)
- Tolmach, E. (4 slides) (Box 8)
  - Bodley gallery, 1968 (Box 8)
- Tommasi (2 slides) (Box 8)
  - Bianchini gallery, 1964 (Box 8)
- Toral, Christobal (2 slides) (Box 8)
  - Staempfli gallery, 1971, 1973 (Box 8)
- Torres-Garcia (6 slides) (Box 8)
  - Parke-Bernet gallery, 1964 (Box 8)
  - Royal Marks gallery, 1969 (Box 8)
  - Emmerich gallery, 1971 (Box 8)
- Tortora (8 slides) (Box 8)
  - East Hampton gallery, 1968, 1969 (Box 8)
- Toys Sculptors Exhibition (3 slides) (Box 8)
  - Various Artists (Box 8)
  - Royal Marks gallery, 1965 (Box 8)
- Town (9 slides) (Box 8)
  - Bonino gallery, 1964 (Box 8)
- Townley, Hugh, b. 1923 (3 slides) (Box 8)
  - Pace gallery, 1964 (Box 8)
- Townsend (4 slides) (Box 8)
  - Daniels gallery, 1965 (Box 8)
  - Byron gallery, 1966 (Box 8)
- Trivigno, Pat (8 slides) (Box 8)
  - Rose Fried gallery, 1969 (Box 8)
- Troller, Fred, b. 1930 (4 slides) (Box 8)
  - Borgenicht gallery, 1965 (Box 8)
- Trova, Ernest Tino (9 slides) (Box 8)
  - Pace gallery, 1968, 1969, 1973 (Box 8)
- True (1 slide) (Box 8)
  - Krasner gallery, 1966 (Box 8)
- Trunk, Herman, 1894-1963 (1 slide) (Box 8)
  - Gimpel-Weitzenhoffer gallery, 1973 (Box 8)
- Tsai, Wen-Ying (36 slides) (Box 8)
  - Amel gallery, 1964, 1965 (Box 8)
  - Wise gallery, 1968 (Box 8)
  - Denise Rene gallery, 1972 (Box 8)
- Truitt, Anne, 1921-2004 (3 slides) (Box 8)
  - Andre Emmerich gallery, 1969 (Box 8)
- Tucker, Forrest (6 slides) (Box 8)
  - Poindexter gallery, 1969 (Box 8)
- Tucker, William, b. 1936 (6 slides) (Box 8)
  - Feigen gallery, 1965 (Box 8)
  - Elkon gallery, 1968 (Box 8)
- Tumarkin, Igael, b. 1933 (3 slides) (Box 8)
  - Byron gallery (Box 8)
- Tum Suden, Richard (15 slides) (Box 8)
  - Tibor de Nagy gallery, 1965, 1966 (Box 8)
  - Hoffman gallery, 1973 (Box 8)
- Twardowicz, Stanley Jan, b. 1917 (8 slides) [Slide box 44] (Box 8)
  - Peridot gallery, 1968, 1970 (Box 8)
- Twirbutt, Josef (18 slides) (Box 8)
  - Grand Central Moderns gallery, 1966, 1967 (Box 8)
- Twombly, Cy, b. 1928 (18 slides) (Box 8)
  - Castelli gallery, 1967, 1968, 1972, 1974, 1982(?) (Box 8)
- Tworkov, Jack, 1900-1982 (2 slides) (Box 8)
  - French & Co. gallery, 1971 (Box 8)
- Uecker, Gunther, b. 1930 (11 slides) (Box 8)
  - Wise gallery, 1964, 1966 (Box 8)
- Umbreit, William C. (4 slides) (Box 8)
  - Stone gallery, 1971 (Box 8)
- Urban, Reva (6 slides) (Box 8)
  - Grippi-Waddell gallery, 1965 (Box 8)
- Urry, Steven, b. 1939 (1 slide) (Box 8)
  - Zabriskie gallery, 1 (Box 8)
- Uwe (1 slide) (Box 8)
  - Ange gallery, 1969 (Box 8)
- Vagliano, Sally (5 slides) (Box 8)
  - Sachs gallery, 1982(?) (Box 8)
- Van Buren, Richard, b. 1937 (4 slides) (Box 8)
  - Bykert gallery, 1970 (Box 8)
  - Paula Cooper, 1975 (Box 8)
- Van Dalen (5 slides) (Box 8)
  - Graham gallery, 1970, 1971 (Box 8)
- Vandersluis (3 slides) (Box 8)
  - Krasner gallery, 1969 (Box 8)
- Van der Wiele (5 slides) (Box 8)
  - Peridot gallery, 1969 (Box 8)
- Van Hoeydonck, Paul, b. 1925 (33 slides) (Box 8)
  - Elkon gallery, 1964 (Box 8)
  - Grippi-Waddell gallery, 1965 (Box 8)
  - Waddell gallery, 1967, 1969, 1971 (Box 8)
- Van Leydon (1 slide) (Box 8)
  - Jackson gallery, 1965 (Box 8)
- Van Saun, John (3 slides) (Box 8)
  - Feigen gallery, 1971 (Box 8)
- Vaquero (4 slides) (Box 8)
  - Kreisler gallery, 1969 (Box 8)
- Varga, Margit (2 slides) (Box 8)
  - Midtown gallery, 1970 (Box 8)
- Varney (3 slides) (Box 8)
  - Wickersham gallery, 1969 (Box 8)
- Vasa (1 slide) (Box 8)
  - Sachs gallery, 1967 (Box 8)
- Vass, Gene (14 slides) (Box 8)
  - Schaefer gallery, 1967, 1969 (Box 8)
- Vasarely, Victor, 1906-1997 (54 slides) (Box 8)
  - Chalette gallery, 1964 (Box 8)
  - Pace gallery, 1964, 1965 (Box 8)
  - AFA gallery, 1966 (Box 8)
  - Denise Rene gallery, 1972 (Box 8)
  - M. Jackson gallery, n.d. (Box 8)
- Vidal (1 slide) [Slide box 45] (Box 8)
  - Bonino gallery, 1968 (Box 8)
- Vilder (1 slide) (Box 8)
  - Wise gallery, 1968 (Box 8)
- Villa, Carlos (3 slides) (Box 8)
  - Hoffmann gallery, 1973 (Box 8)
- Vines, Frank L. (2 slides) (Box 8)
  - Fischbach gallery, 1966 (Box 8)
- Visionaries, USCO (show including Isaac Abrams, Alan Atwell, William Barrell, Peter Dean, Klarwein, and Robert Yasuda) (8 slides) (Box 8)
  - East Hampton, 1967 (Box 8)
- Vivona, Linda (2 slides) (Box 8)
  - Graham gallery, 1971 (Box 8)
- Vodicka, Ruth, b. 1921 (1 slide) (Box 8)
  - Sachs gallery, 1964 (Box 8)
- Von Ringelheim, Paul (6 slides) (Box 8)
  - Rose Fried gallery, 1964 (Box 8)
  - OK Harris gallery, 1971, 1973 (Box 8)
- Von Wicht, John, 1888-1970 (9 slides) (Box 8)
  - Schaefer gallery, 1966, 1967 (Box 8)
- Voss, Jan, b. 1945 (10 slides) (Box 8)
  - Lefebre gallery, 1966 (Box 8)
- Von Weigand, Charmion, 1898-1983 (12 slides) (Box 8)
  - Parke Bernet gallery, 1964 (Box 8)
  - Chalette gallery, 1964 (Box 8)
  - Howard Wise gallery, 1964, 1965 (Box 8)
- Waddell, Eugene (11 slides) (Box 8)
  - Spectrum gallery, 1967 (Box 8)
- Wakita (5 slides) (Box 8)
  - M. Jackson gallery, 1969 (Box 8)
- Walberg (3 slides) (Box 8)
  - Royal Marks, 1969 (Box 8)
- Walker, John, b. 1939 (6 slides) (Box 8)
  - Reese Palley, 1971, 1972 (Box 8)
- Walotsky, Ron (1 slide) (Box 8)
  - Spectrum gallery, 1968 (Box 8)
- Walton, William (7 slide) (Box 8)
  - Graham gallery (Box 8)
- Warhol, Andy, 1928-1987 (12 slides) (Box 8)
  - Leo Castelli gallery, 1964, 1966 (Box 8)
- Watts, Robert, 1923-1988 (2 slides) (Box 8)
  - Bianchini gallery, 1966 (Box 8)
- Wardlaw, George (1 slide) (Box 8)
  - Allan Stone gallery, 1964 (Box 8)
- Weber, Idelle, b. 1932 (2 slides) (Box 8)
  - 100 Acres gallery, 1973 (Box 8)
- Weichsel (1 slide) (Box 8)
  - Graham gallery, 1969 (Box 8)
- Weinrib, David, b. 1924 (2 slides) (Box 8)
  - Royal Marks gallery, 1971 (Box 8)
- Weiss, Edward (23 slides) (Box 8)
  - Jackson gallery, 1966 (Box 8)
- Welch, Roger, b. 1946 (4 slides) (Box 8)
  - Gibson gallery, 1973 (Box 8)
- Welliver, Neil G., 1929-2005 (13 slides) (Box 8)
  - Tibor de Nagy gallery, 1969, 1970 (Box 8)
  - Myers gallery, 1971, 1972 (Box 8)
  - Fischbach gallery, 1975 (Box 8)
- Wells, Mac (5 slides) (Box 8)
  - Sachs gallery, 1967 (Box 8)
  - Hutchinson gallery, 1972 (Box 8)
- Wending (2 slides) (Box 8)
  - Circ. Lib. Ptg. Gallery, 1966 (Box 8)
- Wesley, John, b. 1928 (2 slides) (Box 8)
  - Elkon gallery, 1971 (Box 8)
- Westerman (4 slides) (Box 8)
  - Frumkin gallery, 1965, 1967 (Box 8)
  - Dwan gallery, 1968 (Box 8)
- Whanki (Kim Hwan-gi, 1913-1974) (6 slides) (Box 8)
  - Tasca gallery, 1966 (Box 8)
- Wiley, William T., b. 1937 (4 slides) (Box 8)
  - Staempfli gallery, 1964 (Box 8)
- Wilke, Ulfert S., 1907-1988 (3 slides) (Box 8)
  - Wise gallery, 1964 (Box 8)
- Will, Dennis (6 slides) (Box 8)
  - XX Century West gallery, 1967 (Box 8)
- Willenbecher, John, b. 1936 (5 slides) (Box 8)
  - Feigen gallery, 1966, 1968 (Box 8)
- Williams, Neil, 1934-1988 (12 slides) [Slide box 46] (Box 8)
  - Green gallery, 1964 (Box 8)
  - Andre Emmerich gallery, 1966, 1968 (Box 8)
- Williams, Paul (4 slides) (Box 8)
  - Wise gallery, 1970 (Box 8)
- Williams, Roger, b. 1943 (1 slide) (Box 8)
  - Andre Emmerich gallery, 1973 (Box 8)
- Williams, William Thomas, b. 1942 (4 slides) (Box 8)
  - Reese-Palley gallery, 1971 (Box 8)
- Willis, Thornton, b. 1936 (2 slides) (Box 8)
  - Paley and Lowe gallery, 1971 (Box 8)
- Wilmarth, Christopher Mallory, 1943-1987 (8 slides) (Box 8)
  - Graham gallery, 1968 (Box 8)
  - Paula Cooper gallery, 1971, 1972 (Box 8)
- Wilson (1 slide) (Box 8)
  - Bodley gallery, 1972 (Box 8)
- Wilson, Jane, b. 1924 (24 slides) (Box 8)
  - Tibor de Nagy gallery, 1966 (Box 8)
  - Fischbach gallery, 1966, 1981, 1982, 1983 (Box 8)
  - Graham gallery, 1968, 1971 (Box 8)
- Wilson, Jim (1 slide) (Box 8)